The Git Times — Wednesday, September 16, 2026
Agent Skill Transforms Text Prompts Into Interactive 3D Scenes Without Manual Coding
Combines Claude Code and Codex plugins with 223 recipes to generate Three.js/Blender visualizations from natural language
AI: Netdata v2.11.0 Adds AI Troubleshooting and Network Monitoring for DevOps Teams
Robotics: QuestDB 10.0.1 sharpens real-time analytics with faster protocol and smoother Live Views
Cyber: Authelia Adds Quantum-Resistant Login Options for Web Apps
Systems: Vercel Labs’ fx Brings Unix-Style Coding Agents to Zig Binary to AI-Powered Terminal Workflows
DIY: Pulp Platform Updates AXI IP With ID Width Fixes and CI Improvements
GameDev: PlayCanvas Engine Adds Gaussian Splatting Support for Real-Time 3D Rendering
"The daily paper for people who build."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com